Digital Media Department; Collection ua395
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Born-Digital Photographs, 1999-2019
  - Unsorted University photographs, 1999-2004
    - A display of international and domestic products..., Undated
    - University at Albany students Meagan Cooley,..., 2002 September 7
    - University at Albany students form an assembly..., 2002 September 7
    - Unidentified persons and University at Albany..., 2002 September 7
    - Trina Thomas Patterson speaking to a Fox 23 news..., 2002 May 6
    - International SEMATECH CEO C. Robert Helms speaks..., 2002 September 11
    - International SEMATECH CEO C. Robert Helms speaks..., 2002 September 11
    - International SEMATECH CEO C. Robert Helms..., 2002 September 11
    - International SEMATECH CEO C. Robert Helms shakes..., 2002 September 11
    - IBM Senior Vice President and Director of Research..., 2002 September 11
    - IBM Senior Vice President and Director of Research..., 2002 September 11
    - Unidentified audience members listen to an address..., 2002 September 11
    - Unidentified audience members listen to an address..., 2002 September 11
    - IBM Senior Vice President and Director of Research..., 2002 September 11
    - Unidentified persons listen to a presentation at..., 2002 September 11
    - An unidentified person exits the Arts and Sciences..., 2002 September 24
    - An unidentified person enters the Arts and..., 2002 September 24
    - Exterior photo of the Arts and Sciences building..., 2002 September 24
    - An unidentified person poses in the Arts and..., 2002 September 24
    - Unidentified persons walk inside the Arts and..., 2002 September 24
    - Classes in the newly renovated Humanities Building..., 2003 September 2
    - Classes in the newly renovated Humanities Building..., 2003 September 2
    - Interior photo of the Arts and Sciences building..., 2002 September 24
    - Interior photo of the Arts and Sciences building..., 2002 September 24
    - Interior photo of the Arts and Sciences building..., 2002 September 24
    - Professor of Chemistry Eric Block speaks at the..., Undated
    - Professor of Chemistry Eric Block and an..., Undated
    - Regional Food Bank of Northeastern New York..., 2002 September 7
    - University at Albany students load boxes of corn..., 2002 September 7
    - University at Albany Athletic Director Lee McElroy..., 2002 May 6
    - Dean of the College of Computing and Information..., 2003 September 5
    - Dean of the School of Education Susan Phillips..., 2003 September 5
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2003 September 5
    - Associate Professor of Business Paul Miesling,..., 2003 September 5
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2003 September 5
    - University at Albany Provost Carlos Santiago..., 2003 September 5
    - Dean of the School of Education Susan Phillips..., 2003 September 5
    - Dean of the School of Education Susan Phillips..., 2003 September 5
    - Dean of the College of Computing and Information..., 2003 September 5
    - University at Albany Provost Carlos Santiago..., 2003 September 5
    - An unidentified person speaks at an exhibit..., 2003 September 5
    - Unidentified University at Albany faculty and..., 2003 September 5
    - at a reception for the School of Education at the..., 2003 September 5
    - An unidentified person at the podium addresses the..., 2002 September 11
    - An unidentified person addresses the audience at..., 2002 September 12
    - Nixon Peabody LLP partner Marc Kaufman presents at..., 2002 September 12
    - International SEMATECH CEO C. Robert Helms speaks..., 2002 September 12
    - International SEMATECH CEO C. Robert Helms speaks..., 2002 September 12
    - International SEMATECH CEO C. Robert Helms..., 2002 September 12
    - Unidentified individuals attend an address at the..., 2002 September 12
    - International SEMATECH CEO C. Robert Helms shakes..., 2002 September 12
    - Aseem Sharma from Corning International speaks at..., 2002 September 12
    - Professor of Chemistry Eric Block shakes hands..., Undated
    - Professor of Chemistry Eric Block speaks at the..., Undated
    - University of Albany students harvested corn, like..., 2002 September 7
    - A volunteer opens an ear of corn at a harvest..., 2002 September 7
    - University at Albany students load boxes of corn..., 2002 September 7
    - Trina Thomas Patterson named head coach of the..., 2002 May 6
    - University at Albany Athletic Director Lee McElroy..., 2002 May 6
    - University at Albany Athletic Director Lee McElroy..., 2002 May 6